A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.26 (A2000) FA470
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2000.049: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1982-2000; AC.2000.049; 3.6 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3341-R3343.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3341-R3343.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.049.1
    - RF 95010 #66 - FAMILY CARE INTERNATIONAL- GOVERNMENTS: SEXUAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND RIGHTS, 1995-1997 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95010 A 67 - GUTTMACHER INSTITUTE - CHARTBOOK ON WOMEN'S STATUS, REPRODUCTIVE BEHAVIOR AND POPULATION DYNAMICS, 1994-1999; 2 folders. (Box R3343)
    - RF 95018 #58 - ORGANIZACION DE EJIDOS FORESTALES DE LA ZONA MAYA (MEXICO) - NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT, 1993-1999 (Box R3343)
- AC.2000.051: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-1999; AC.2000.051; 2.4 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3344-R3345.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3344-R3345.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.051.1
    - RF 95018 #62 - NELSON, KRISTEN CAROL- SSRF: RURAL AGRICULTURAL SYSTEMS, 1992-1998 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95019 #13 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - THIRD INTERNATIONAL MEETING OF CASSAVA BIOTECHNOLOGY NETWORK, 1995-1996 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95023 #31 - UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA - IDENTIFY CONTEMPORARY ENGLISH-LANGUAGE MUSLIM WRITINGS THAT REFLECT VALUE OF PLURALISTIC DIALOGUE, 1996-1998 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95023 #34 - ASHTAR FOR THEATRE EDUCATION AND TRAINING (ISRAEL) - "MARTYRS ARE COMING BACK...", 1996-1997 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95023 #35 - CENTER FOR PALESTINE RESEARCH AND STUDIES (ISRAEL) - PUBLIC OPINION POLL, ELECTORAL BEHAVIOR AND TRANSITION TO DEMOCRACY PROJECT, 1995-1997 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95024 #242 - DANCE THEATRE FOUNDATION (DBA ALVIN AILEY DANCE THEATER FOUNDATION) - COLLABORATIVE DANCE WORK, "RIVERSIDE", 1995-1998 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95025 #206 - APPALSHOP - WORKSHOP: FUTURE OF THE NOT-FOR-PROFIT MEDIA ARTS FIELD, 1995-1998 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95025 #207 - WHITNEY MUSEUM OF AMERICAN ART - CONFERENCE, "THE AMERICAN AVANT GARDE: HISTORICAL DIS/CONTINUITIES IN FILM AND VIDEO, 1995-1997 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95025 #209 - NATIONAL ALLIANCE OF MEDIA ARTS CENTERS - DOCUMENTING CONFERENCE ON CULTURAL EQUITY IN 21ST CENTURY, 1995-1997 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95025 #232 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - 1996 AFRICAN FILM FESTIVAL, 1995-1997 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95025 #237 - CIVIL RIGHTS PROJECT - CIVIL RIGHTS TELECOMMUNICATIONS FORUM, 1996-1999 (Box R3344)
    - RF 95027 A 122 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER OF PHOTOGRAPHY - EXHIBITION "NAGASAKI JOURNEY: THE PHOTOGRAPHS OF YOSUKE YAMAHATA", 1995-1997 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 125 - FABRIC WORKSHOP - COMMISSIONING PROGRAM "CHANGING SPACES", 1995-1998 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 126 - AMERICAN CRAFT MUSEUM - EXHIBITION "CRAFT IN THE MACHINE AGE 1920-1945", 1994-1997 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 128 - NEW MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - "A LABOR OF LOVE" EXHIBITION, 1994-1997 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 129 - BARD COLLEGE - "BETWEEN HEAVEN HELL: CONTEMPORARY ART FROM THE MIDDLE EASTERN DIASPORA", 1994-1996 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 130 - NATIONAL AUTONOMOUS UNIVERSITY OF MEXICO - HISTORY OF LATIN AMERICAN ART, 1995-1996 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 131 - GUGGENHEIM FOUNDATION - "AFRICA: THE ART OF A CONTINENT", 1995-1997 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 133 - FEDERATION OF STATE HUMANITIES COUNCILS - EXHIBITION: "PRODUCE FOR VICTORY: POSTERS AND THE AMERICAN HOME FRONT 1941-1945", 1993-1998 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 134 - UNIVERSITY OF NOTRE DAME - SNITE MUSEUM OF ART - EXHIBITION "RITUAL BALLGAME", 1995-1998 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 136 - FONDO DEL SOL - LOIS MAILOU JONES EXHIBITION, 1995-1996 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 A 137 - FONDO DEL SOL - "THE ART OF SANTERO -A LIVING TRADITION" EXHIBITION, 1995-1998 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95027 #138 - MOORE COLLEGE OF ART AND DESIGN - CATALOGUE FOR "PRISON SENTENCES: THE PRISON AS SITE/THE PRISON AS SUBJECT", 1994-1996 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95039 #39 - TRANSVAAL SCHOOL OF PUBLIC HEALTH (SOUTH AFRICA)- QUALITY ASSURANCE MANAGEMENT METHODS COURSE, 1996-1997 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95043 #25 - UNIVERSITY OF GHANA - ESTABLISH INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR AFRICAN MUSIC AND DANCE, 1991-1997 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95046 #1 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS INTERNSHIP, 1995-1998 (Box R3345)
    - RF 95046 #3 - PANAMERICAN AGRICULTURAL COLLEGE (HONDURAS) - TRANSGENIC BACILLUS THURINGIENSIS CROPS IN MESOAMERICAN AGRICULTURE WORKSHOP, 1996-1998 (Box R3345)
- AC.2000.055: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-1999; AC.2000.055; 2.4 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3346-R3347.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3346-R3347.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.055.1
    - RF 95046 #5 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES AT LOS BANOS - BIOSAFETY ASPECTS OF AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY WORKSHOP, 1996-1998 (Box R3346)
    - RF 95046 #6 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BIOSAFETY ASPECTS OF AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY WORKSHOP, 1996 (Box R3346)
    - RF 95052 #89 - KINGS MAJESTIC CORPORATION - "WORLD SERIES" PROJECT, 1995-1997 (Box R3346)
    - RF 95052 #91 - SPOLETO FESTIVAL USA - 1996 FESTIVAL SEASON (Box R3346)
    - RF 95055 #3 - NATIONAL ASSEMBLY OF LOCAL ARTS AGENCIES - NATIONAL AWARENESS OF VALUE OF THE ARTS, 1994-1997 (Box R3346)
    - RF 95055 #3 - NATIONAL ASSEMBLY OF LOCAL ARTS AGENCIES - NATIONAL AWARENESS OF VALUE OF THE ARTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1997 (Box R3346)
    - RF 95063 - TEXAS INTERFAITH EDUCATION FUND - SCHOOL REFORM MOBILIZATION, 1989-1996; 3 folders. (Box R3346)
    - RF 96001 #404 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR XIAO HAN, 1995-1999 (Box R3347)
    - RF 96001 #405 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH - BIOTECHNOLOGY AND IMPROVEMENT OF INDICA RICE, 1990-1999; 2 folders. (Box R3347)
    - RF 96001 #413 - UNIVERSITY OF PERADENIYA (SRI LANKA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR ATHULA PERERA, 1995-1999 (Box R3347)
    - RF 96001 #417 - FUDAN UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - PHYSICAL MAPPING OF RICE GENOME, 1991-1999 (Box R3347)
    - RF 96001 #434 - THAI RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - ESTABLISH RICE DROUGHT SCREENING FACILITY AT THE UBON RICE RESEARCH CENTER, 1993-1999 (Box R3347)
- AC.2000.056: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1969-2000; AC.2000.056; 4.8 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3348-R3351.; 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3348-R3351.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.056.1
    - RF 96001 #454 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES)- DNA FINGERPRINTING FOR RICE PATHOGENS, BACTERIAL BLIGHT AND BLAST, 1995-1999 (Box R3348)
    - RF 96001 #465 - MALAYSIAN AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE (MALAYSIA) - SCREENING OF TRANSGENIC RICE EXPRESSING COAT PROTEIN(S) OF RICE TUNGRO SPHERICAL VIRUS, 1994-1997 (Box R3348)
    - RF 96001 #470 - UNIVERSITY OF PHILIPPINES AT LOS BANOS - DETECTION AND MONITORING XANTHOMONAS ORYZAE PV. ORYZICOLA, 1992-1999 (Box R3348)
    - RF 96001 #475 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - PRODUCTION OF TRANSGENIC RICE CONTAINING INSECT RESISTANCE GENES, 1994-1998 (Box R3348)
    - RF 96001 #488 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR JIN DEMING, 1995-1999 (Box R3348)
    - RF 96001 #495 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - TRAINING IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY AT TEXAS A&M UNIVERSITY, 1994-2000 (Box R3348)
    - RF 96011 #83 - NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT (KENYA) - TECHNICAL EXCHANGE OF SOUTH-TO SOUTH INITIATIVE WORKSHOP, 1996 (Box R3348)
    - RF 96031 #1 - TASK FORCE FOR CHILD SURVIVAL AND DEVELOPMENT - "CHILDREN FIRST: A GLOBAL FORUM" CONFERENCE, 1996-1997 (Box R3348)
    - RF 96034 #109 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP ON CLINICAL TRIAL OF STD TREATMENT FOR HIV PREVENTION, 1996-1997 (Box R3348)
  - United States, 200
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 200A
      - 200A - POPULATION COUNCIL - FERTILIZATION, 1978-1983 (Box R3349)
      - 200A - SLOAN KETTERING INSTITUTE (FOR CANCER RESEARCH) - REPRODUCTIVE IMMUNOLOGY, 1978-1983 (Box R3349)
      - 200A - TEMPLE UNIVERSITY - RNA IN REPRODUCTION AND DEVELOPMENT, 1978-1983 (Box R3349)
      - 200A - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA - REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY, 1969-1982; 2 folders. (Box R3349)
      - 200A - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA - REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1969-1982; 3 folders. (Box R3350)
      - 200A - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS - POPULATION CONTROL, 1971-1983 (Box R3350)
      - 200A - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS - POPULATION CONTROL - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1971-1983 (Box R3350)
    - United States - Population Studies, 200P
      - 200P - CEDARS-SINAl MEDICAL CENTER - HCG-LIKE PROTEIN, 1979-1983 (Box R3350)
      - 200P - GORDON RESEARCH CONFERENCE ? FERTILIZATION CONFERENCE, 1980-1982 (Box R3350)
      - 200P - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND - OOCYTE MATURATION INHIBITOR, 1979-1983 (Box R3350)
  - Thailand (Siam), 617
    - 617 - SIAM - PUBLIC HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) ? CONTRACEPTIVE IMPLANTS, 1978-1983 (Box R3350)
  - Israel, 825
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, 825A
      - 825A - HEBREW UNIVERSITY OF JERUSALEM - REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY, 1978-1983 (Box R3350)
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2000.056.2
    - AH 9273 - WORLD INSTITUTE FOR DEVELOPMENT ECONOMICS RESEARCH - MEETING ON "ALTERNATIVE APPROACHES TO GREENING OF ECONOMICS", 1991-1996 (Box R3351)
    - AH 9273 - WORLD INSTITUTE FOR DEVELOPMENT ECONOMICS RESEARCH - MEETING ON "ALTERNATIVE APPROACHES TO GREENING OF ECONOMICS" - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-1996 (Box R3351)
    - AH 9315 - NATIONAL HUMANITIES ALLIANCE - EDUCATE CONGRESS ON VALUE OF SCHOLARLY RESEARCH IN THE HUMANITIES, 1992-1998 (Box R3351)
    - AH 9344 - NATIONAL HUMANITIES CENTER - LATIN AMERICAN CIVIL SOCIETY PROJECT, 1992-1998 (Box R3351)
    - AH 9345 - CENTER FOR PSYCHOSOCIAL STUDIES - CONTEMPORARY CHINA SOCIAL AND CULTURAL CRITICISM, 1990-1997 (Box R3351)
    - AH 9356 - NATIONAL RELIGIOUS PARTNERSHIP FOR THE ENVIRONMENT - CAMPAIGN FOR GLOBAL SUSTAINABILITY AND JUSTICE, 1990-1997 (Box R3351)
    - AH 9356 - NATIONAL RELIGIOUS PARTNERSHIP FOR THE ENVIRONMENT - CAMPAIGN FOR GLOBAL SUSTAINABILITY AND JUSTICE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-1997 (Box R3351)
    - 94-8010-25 - AMERICAN COMPOSER'S ORCHESTRA, INC - SONIDO DE LAS AMERICAS: MUSIC OF VENEZUELA AND BRASIL, 1992-1996 (Box R3351)
- AC.2000.059: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-1998; AC.2000.059; 2.4 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3352-R3353.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3352-R3353.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2000.059.1
    - AH 9455 - MEDIATION NETWORK FOR NORTHERN IRELAND - PEACE-MAKING AND CONFLICT RESOLUTION, 1994-1996 (Box R3352)
    - AH 9502 - JEWISH MUSEUM - CONFERENCE "ASSIMILATION AND CULTURAL RETENTION", 1994-1997 (Box R3352)
    - AH 9503 - CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK- CONFERENCE ON LESBIAN AND GAY HISTORY, 1995-1997 (Box R3352)
    - AH 9505 - COLORADO COLLEGE - LATINA COMPARATIVE FEMINIST RESEARCH WORK GROUP, 1994-1998 (Box R3352)
    - AH 9510 - CAPOEIRA FOUNDATION - QUILOMBOS, 1995-1996 (Box R3352)
    - AH 9511 - ARCADIA PICTURES - "A MORE PERFECT UNION: AMERICANS IN CONVERSATION", 1994-1997 (Box R3352)
    - AH 9515 - FILM SOCIETY OF LINCOLN CENTER - ARAB FILM SERIES PROJECT, 1994-1997 (Box R3352)
    - AH 9516 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF LATINO ARTS AND CULTURE - SECOND ANNUAL CONFERENCE, 1995-1996 (Box R3352)
    - AH 9520 - PEOPLE FOR THE AMERICAN WAY - ANTI-CENSORSHIP, 1990-1997; Total of 3 folders in Boxes R3352 and R3353. (Box R3352)
    - AH 9520 - PEOPLE FOR THE AMERICAN WAY - ANTI-CENSORSHIP, 1990-1997; Total of 3 folders in Boxes R3352 and R3353. (Box R3353)
    - AH 9520 - PEOPLE FOR THE AMERICAN WAY - ANTI-CENSORSHIP - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-1997; Total of 2 folders in Boxes R3352 and R3353. (Box R3352)
    - AH 9520 - PEOPLE FOR THE AMERICAN WAY - ANTI-CENSORSHIP - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-1997; Total of 2 folders in Boxes R3352 and R3353. (Box R3353)
    - AH 9523 - WORLD MUSIC PRODUCTIONS - AFRICAN MUSIC RADIO SERIES, 1996-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3353)
    - AH 9524 - ROYAL ACADEMY OF ARTS (ENGLAND) - CATALOGUE FOR AFRICAN ART EXHIBITION, 1994-1997 (Box R3353)
    - AH 9527 - ORGANIZATION OF AMERICAN HISTORIANS - INTELLECTUAL INTEGRITY OF MUSEUMS/HISTORY STANDARDS, 1995-1998 (Box R3353)
    - AH 9531 - ASIA SOCIETY - ROLE OF ASIAN-AMERICANS IN U.S.-ASIA RELATIONS, 1995-1998 (Box R3353)
- AC.2000.060: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-1999; AC.2000.060; 2.4 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3354-R3355.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3354-R3355.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2000.060.1
    - AH 9533 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - HARVARD GUIDE TO AFRICAN-AMERICAN HISTORY, 1992-1996 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9534 - CENTER FOR ARTS AND CULTURE - SUPPORT FOR GENERAL EXPENSES, 1995-1998 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9537 - NEWBERRY LIBRARY - D'ARCY MCNICKLE CENTER FOR THE HISTORY OF THE AMERICAN INDIAN - INDIAN VOICES IN THE ACADEMY, 1994-1995 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9538 - BREAD AND ROSES CULTURAL PROJECT - CONTRIBUTIONS TO U.S. OF NATIVE AMERICAN WOMEN, 1995-1998 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9543 - GUGGENHEIM FOUNDATION - "IN/SIGHT: FIVE DECADES OF AFRICAN PHOTOGRAPHERS 1940 TO THE PRESENT, 1995-1997 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9546 - STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK (BINGHAMTON) - CONFERENCE ON THE AFRICAN DIASPORA, 1995-1996 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9547 - LIBRARIES FOR THE FUTURE - CIVIL LIBRARY PROJECT, 1995-1999 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9548 - MEET THE COMPOSER, INC. - NEW RESIDENCIES PROGRAM, 1994-1997 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9549 - NATIONAL PUERTO RICAN COALITION - CONFERENCE: ADVANCING THE PUERTO RICAN COMMUNITY INTO THE 21ST CENTURY, 1995-1996 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9550 - WOLFSON FOUNDATION OF DECORATIVE AND PROPAGANDA ARTS - CUBA THEME ISSUE OF JOURNAL OF DECORATIVE AND PROPAGANDA ARTS, 1995-1997 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9602 - ANTORCHAS FOUNDATION (ARGENTINA) - CONFERENCE, "CULTURE AND NATION IN LATIN AMERICA, 1994-1997 (Box R3354)
    - AH 9610 - LUMIERE PRODUCTIONS, INC. - TELEVISION SERIES, "WITH GOD ON OUR SIDE: THE RISE OF THE RELIGIOUS RIGHT IN AMERICA", 1993-1998 (Box R3355)
    - AH 9610 - LUMIERE PRODUCTIONS, INC. - TELEVISION SERIES, "WITH GOD ON OUR SIDE: THE RISE OF THE RELIGIOUS RIGHT IN AMERICA" - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-1998 (Box R3355)
    - AH 9614 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - HUMANITIES IN THE UNITED STATES TODAY, 1996-1998 (Box R3355)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2000.060.2
    - AS 9206 - SAVIDAN, YVES - APOMIXIS NEWSLETTER, 1991-1999 (Box R3355)
    - AS 9306 - MALAWI -AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (DEPT. OF) - PLANT NUTRIENT AVAILABILITY, DEPLETED SOILS ASSESSMENT & FERTILIZERS REHABILITATION, 1990-1997 (Box R3355)
    - AS 9311 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - REVISIT ECONOMIC PROJECTIONS OF THE 1960s RE: INDIA, 1993-1995 (Box R3355)
    - AS 9313 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI - BEAN PATHOLOGY, 1989-1997 (Box R3355)
    - AS 9315 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY(KENYA) - EVALUATE LEUCAENA ACCESSIONS, 1992-1999 (Box R3355)
    - AS 9323 - SITHOLE, GORDON -AGRICULTURAL PRICING AND MARKETING IN ZIMBABWE, 1993-1995 (Box R3355)
    - AS 9333 - JOHN INNES INSTITUTE - BIOTECHNOLOGY RESEARCH, 1989-1999 (Box R3355)
- AC.2000.061: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1984-2000; AC.2000.061; 3.6 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3356-R3358.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3356-R3358.
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2000.061.1
    - 94-8100-10 - UNITED STATES-AGRICULTURE (DEPARTMENT OF) - PLANT GENOME III MEETING, 1994-2000 (Box R3356)
    - 94-8100-14 - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT - ENABLE ALUMNI RESEARCHERS TO PARTICIPATE IN A WORKSHOP AND A CONFERENCE, 1993-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9433 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - AFRICAN PARTICIPATION AT THE XTH SYMPOSIUM OF THE INTERNATIONAL SOCIETY FOR TROPICAL ROOT CROPS, 1994-1998 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9436 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (IITA) (NIGERIA) - URBAN UTILIZATION OF CASSAVA IN TANZANIA AND ZANZIBAR, 1994-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9437 - COMMONWEALTH SCIENTIFIC AND INDUSTRIAL RESEARCH ORGANIZATION (CSIRO) - APOMIXIS IN ARABADOPSIS THALIANA, 1992-1998 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9441 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRI-BIOTECHNOLOGY APPLICATIONS - BIOSAFETY REGULATIONS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1994-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9441 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRI-BIOTECHNOLOGY APPLICATIONS - BIOSAFETY REGULATIONS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9504 - REHABILITATION OF ARID ENVIRONMENTS CHARITABLE TRUST (KENYA) - DATA BASE FOR VIABLE LAND-MANAGEMENT AT BARINGO DISTRICT, 1994-1996 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9506 - TEXAS A&M UNIVERSITY - HARNESSING APOMIXIS CONFERENCE, 1994-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9507 - NEW YORK ZOOLOGICAL SOCIETY - PHOTOGRAPHY AND MAPPING WORK IN KITENGELA CONSERVATION AREA IN KENYA, 1994-1996 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9508 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - LAND TENURE AND SUSTAINABLE MANAGEMENT OF TREE RESOURCES IN UGANDA, 1994-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9509 - INTERNATIONAL IRRIGATION MANAGEMENT INSTITUTE (SRI LANKA) - CGIAR INTERCENTER PROGRAM ON WATER RESOURCE MANAGEMENT, 1995-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9510 - UNIVERSIDAD AUTONOMA DE YUCATAN (MEXICO) - FERTILITY IN MAIZE-LEGUME SYSTEMS IN YUCATAN AND VERACRUZ, 1994-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9511 - UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA (GAINESVILLE) - GLOBAL RESEARCH ON ENVIRONMENTAL AND AGRICULTURAL NEXUS INITIATIVE (GREAN), 1994-2000 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9512 - UNITED STATES - AGRICULTURE (DEPT. OF) - PLANT GENOME IV MEETING, 1995-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9514 - COLEGIO DE POSTGRADUADOS (MEXICO) - IV INTERNATIONAL COURSE ON DESERTIFICATION AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT FOR LATIN AMERICA AND CARIBBEAN, 1995 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9518 - TECHNOSERVE - INVENTORY CREDIT AND SMALLHOLDER MAIZE PRODUCTION IN KENYA, 1995-1996 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9519 - OKOTH, PETER F. - SOIL EROSION AND IMPACT BY LAND USE, 1995-1997 (Box R3356)
    - AS 9520 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - SOCIO-ECONOMICS CONFERENCE, 1995-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9521 - MALINDI, ELLARD S. - FACTORS AFFECTING TECHNOLOGY UPTAKE BY SMALLHOLDER FARMERS IN MALAWI, 1995-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9522 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (KENYA) - STRATEGIES AND IMPLEMENTATION, 1995-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9523 - MEXICAN FOUNDATION FOR ENVIRONMENTAL EDUCATION - HORTICULTURE IN XOCHITLA, 1995-1996 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9524 - INTERNATIONAL FERTILIZER DEVELOPMENT CENTER (IFDC) - FARM LEVEL MODELING FOR NATURAL RESOURCE USE IN URUGUAY, 1993-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9526 - INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGY OF OAXACA (MEXICO) - VETIVER NURSERY, 1995-1999 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9527 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (KENYA) - SOCIAL SCIENCES DEPARTMENT CONSULTANCY, 1995-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9528 - KENYA FORESTRY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - FIRST KENYA NATIONAL AGROFORESTRY CONFERENCE, 1995-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9529 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - 15TH ANNUAL CONFERENCE OF THE SOIL SCIENCE SOCIETY OF EAST AFRICA, 1995-1996 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9530 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - SOIL AND WATER CONSERVATION SOCIETY OF UGANDA WORKSHOP, 1995 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9534 - OGWANG, JAMES A - DECISION TOOLS FOR PEST MANAGEMENT, 1994-1998 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9535 - RESEARCH CENTRE FOR AGROFORESTRY IN AMAZONIA (BRAZIL) - SHIFTING CULTIVATION IN WESTERN AMAZON, 1995-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9538 - NJUGUNA, STEPHEN K. - MACROECONOMIC STABILIZATION ON THE KENYAN AGRICULTURAL SECTOR, 1995-1998 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9539 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - GEOGRAPHIC INFORMATION SYSTEMS CHARACTERIZATION SOFTWARE, 1995-1998 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9542 - CAB INTERNATIONAL - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR BIOLOGICAL CONTROL (ENGLAND) - LARGER GRAIN BORER IN EAST AND SOUTHERN AFRICA MEETING, 1995-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9543 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - TRAINING PROGRAM ON DSSAT CROP GROWTH MODELS, 1995-1996 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9546 - CARRANZA, TZINNIA - SUSTAINABILITY OF MAIZE-LEGUME SMALLHOLDERS IN CHIMALAPAS, MEXICO, 1995-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9549 - HILLEL, DANIEL - HIGH-FREQUENCY IRRIGATION AND TECHNOLOGY TRANSFER TO AFRICA, 1995-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9603 - MALAWI-AGRICULTURE AND LIVESTOCK DEVELOPMENT (MINISTRY OF) - MALAWI MAIZE PRODUCTIVITY TASK FORCE, 1995-1998 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9612 - NYIRENDA, MARGARET M. - FELLOWSHIP AT HARVARD UNIVERSITY'S KENNEDY SCHOOL OF GOVERNMENT, 1994-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9627 - CARTER CENTER - AGRICULTURAL ASSESSMENT IN NORTH KOREA, 1996-1997 (Box R3357)
    - AS 9640 - ROCKEFELLER UNIVERSITY - RICE GENES REGULATION, 1984-1996 (Box R3358)
    - 94-8020-18 - URBAN INSTITUTE - TRANSITION FROM WELFARE TO WORK, 1994-1997 (Box R3358)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2000.061.2
    - EO 9501 - CENTER FOR STRATEGIC AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - MILITARY PERSONNEL AND INNER CITY YOUTH DEVELOPMENT, 1994-1997 (Box R3358)
    - EO 9507 - CITY PARKS FOUNDATION - WELFARE RECIPIENTS TRAINING PROGRAM, 1993-1996; 3 folders. (Box R3358)
- AC.2000.063: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2000; AC.2000.063; 3.6 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3359, R3360, R3362.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3359, R3360, R3362.
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2000.063.1
    - EO 9511 - CHAPIN HALL CENTER FOR CHILDREN - PUBLISH VOLUME ON COMMUNITY-BUILDING INITIATIVES, 1994-2000 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9512 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL- UNIVERSAL ACCESS TO INFORMATION AGE RESOURCES, 1994-1998 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9516 - LAWYERS' COMMITTEE FOR CIVIL RIGHTS UNDER LAW - ADDRESS ASSAULTS ON AFFIRMATIVE ACTION, 1995-1998 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9518 - PRIVATE INDUSTRY COUNCIL OF MILWAUKEE COUNTY - MILWAUKEE JOBS CONNECTION, 1995-1997 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9519 - DEVELOPMENT FUND - LESSONS OF CALIFORNIA ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT LENDING INITIATIVE, 1995-2000 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9521 - INDIANAPOLIS PRIVATE INDUSTRY COUNCIL - SELF-SUFFICIENCY INITIATIVE, 1995-1996 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9522 - LAWYERS' COMMITTEE FOR CIVIL RIGHTS OF THE SAN FRANCISCO BAY AREA - RACE AFFIRMATIVE ACTION; DECREASE SOCIAL AND ETHNIC POLARIZATION, 1995-1997 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9523 - GREATER KANSAS CITY COMMUNITY FOUNDATION - ENTERPRISE COMMUNITIES AND EMPOWERMENT ZONES, 1995-1996 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9524 - GEORGIA STATE UNIVERSITY - EMPLOYER HIRING BEHAVIOR AND MINORITY JOB APPLICANTS, 1994-1998 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9532 - CENTER FOR COMMUNITY CHANGE - JOBS INITIATIVE, 1994-1997 (Box R3359)
    - EO 9532 - CENTER FOR COMMUNITY CHANGE - JOBS INITIATIVE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1997 (Box R3360)
    - EO 9601 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - AFFIRMATIVE ACTION IN THE UNITED STATES, 1995-1997 (Box R3360)
    - EO 9606 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - FEDERAL EMPOWERMENT ZONE/ENTERPRISE COMMUNITY INITIATIVE MEETING, 1996-2000 (Box R3360)
  - Health Sciences (HS), AC.2000.063.2
    - HS 9329 - FAMILY CARE INTERNATIONAL - MATERNAL HEALTH AND FAMILY PLANNING, 1992-1997 (Box R3360)
    - HS 9330 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - TROPICAL DISEASE RESEARCH PROGRAM - RESEARCH NEEDS FOR GLOBAL INFECTIOUS DISEASE, 1993-1997 (Box R3360)
  - Global Environment (GE), AC.2000.063.3
    - GE 9304 - KING MONGKUT'S INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY THONBURI (THAILAND) - COMPOSTING CANE TRASH PROJECT, 1993-2000 (Box R3362)
    - GE 9307 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - RENEWABLE FUEL UTILIZATION AND IMPROVED TECHNOLOGIES IN THE DEVELOPING WORLD, 1993-2000 (Box R3362)
    - GE 9311 - AFRICARE - PHOTOVOLTAICS RURAL ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT IN ZIMBABWE, 1993-2000 (Box R3362)